nice-layouts.com 2011-12-31

# Nice Layouts | Professional Web & Flash Templates | Privacy Policy

**IMPORTANT INFORMATION**

Nice Layouts has created this privacy policy because we are committed to our website users privacy. 

Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy, and how we treat personally identifiable information collected from our visitors and users. 

**What our Privacy Policy Covers**

This privacy policy covers the manner in which Nice Layouts treats personally identifiable information collected by Nice Layouts through any website owned and operated by Nice Layouts. 

This privacy policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Nice Layouts does not own or control, or of persons that Nice Layouts does not employ or manage, including any third-party content contributors bound by contract and any third-party websites to which Nice Layouts websites link. 

**How We Collect and Use Your Personal Information** You can visit the websites of Nice Layouts without revealing any personal information. However, Nice Layouts needs certain personal information when you choose to purchase our products, register for an affiliate account, receive the Nice Layouts newsletter, or use certain Nice Layouts services. 

Where required, this information may include your personal contact information and/or your company contact information. Nice Layouts will use this information to reply to your questions, to provide you with requested products and services, to set up your member account, and to contact you regarding new products and services. 

By accessing the services of Nice Layouts and voluntarily providing us with the requested personal information, you consent to the collection and use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy. 

**How We Collect and Use Non-Personal Information**

Nice Layouts automatically receives and records non-personal information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page you requested. Nice Layouts may use this aggregated non-personal information to customize the advertising and content you see and to fulfill your requests for certain products and services. However, Nice Layouts does not connect this non-personal data to any personal information collected from you. 

Nice Layouts also allows third party companies that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Again, these cookies are not connected to any personal information. Third party cookie usage is subject to their own privacy policies, and Nice Layouts assumes no responsibility or liability for this usage. What You Need to Know about Information Sharing and Disclosure 

Nice Layouts may disclose your personal information to third parties who work on behalf of Nice Layouts to provide products and services requested by you. We will share personal information for these reasons only with third parties whose privacy policies are consistent with ours or who agree to abide by our policies with respect to personal information. 

Nice Layouts may also disclose your personal information when: 

* We have your explicit consent to share the information for a specified purpose; 

* We need to respond to subpoenas, court orders or such other legal process; 

* We need to protect the personal safety of the users of our websites or defend the rights or property of Nice Layouts; 

* We find that your actions on our websites violate the Nice Layouts Terms of Use document or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services. 

Third Party Collection and Use of Information

Google.com, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads to our users based on their activity on our site and/or other websites. Google does not collect or use personal information (your name, address, email address, or telephone number); if you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by third party companies, click here: http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

**Your Consent**

If you do not consent to the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information as described in this policy, please do not provide any personal information to Nice Layouts. If you have provided personal information to Nice Layouts and no longer consent to its use or disclosure as outlined herein, please notify Nice Layouts at privacy [at] nice-layouts.com . 

**Your Information Security**

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be regarded as 100% secure. However, Nice Layouts protects your information for your privacy and security. In certain areas of our websites, as identified on the site, Nice Layouts uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to protect data transmissions. 

We also safeguard your personal information from unauthorized access through access control procedures, network firewalls and physical security measures. 

Further, Nice Layouts keeps your personal information only as long as necessary to accomplish the purposes identified above or as required by law. 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

Nice Layouts may at any time, without notice to you and in its sole discretion, amend this policy from time to time. Please review this policy periodically. Your continued use of Nice Layouts websites after any such amendments signifies your acceptance thereof. 

**Have Questions or Suggestions? Contact Us**

If you have questions or suggestions about this privacy policy, or your own personal information, please e-mail us at **privacy [at] nice-layouts.com** .
